airmore.com 2018-12-27

# The Privacy Policy for AirMore

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register for our service, subscribe to our newsletter, place an order, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering for our service, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site or software anonymously.

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience
  * To improve our service
  * To improve customer service
  * To send periodic emails

If you subscribe to our newsletter, your email address may be used to send you occasional company news and updates related to product or service information, etc. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

## How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

## Do we use cookies?

Yes, Cookies are small files that a site or software or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site or softwares or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to help us understand and save your preferences for future visits, remember and process the items in your shopping cart, and compile aggregate data about site or software traffic and site or software interaction so that we can offer better site or software experiences and tools in the future.

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website or software, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site or software policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website or software. These third party sites or software have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites or software. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site or software and welcome any feedback about these sites or software.

## Your Consent

By using our site or service, you consent to our privacy policy.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes and update the Privacy Policy modification date on this page.

This policy was last modified on 05/15/2015

airmore.com
